[[{"answers":["Event Horizon","Cosmic Barrier","Particle Horizon","Universal Boundary"],"correct_answer_id":1,"question":"What is the name of the hypothetical boundary beyond which no information or events can affect us due to the expansion of the universe?","id":"dba83c71-6a01-4bc6-bdc8-913cf17a8934"},{"answers":["Kelvin","Celcius","Fahrenheit","Rankine"],"correct_answer_id":0,"question":"Which among the following temperature scale is based upon absolute zero?","id":"cf9a9e7b-aa3b-450c-a8b5-eade6257627f"},{"answers":["Super Conductivity","Laws of Thermodynamics","Newton’s Law of Motion","Faraday’s law of Electromagnetic Induction"],"correct_answer_id":3,"question":"An Electric generator is based on which of the following scientific principles?","id":"9d716acd-8665-4b43-b67b-40d7ff2b488d"},{"answers":["Luminescence","Radioactivity","Pressure","Mass"],"correct_answer_id":1,"question":"Curie the a unit of which of the following?","id":"789857a1-b615-423f-88b9-c85a645a23f1"},{"answers":[" It is always equal to the distance travelled by the object","It can be less than the distance travelled by the object"," It can be greater than the distance travelled by the object","It always less than the distance travelled by the object"],"correct_answer_id":1,"question":"Which of the following is true about displacement of an object?","id":"af1f47f2-98b6-4476-a2ca-586f52b1eca5"}],[{"answers":["cosine of the largest angle between them","sine of the largest angle between them","cosine of the smallest angle between them","sine of the smallest angle between them"],"correct_answer_id":2,"question":"The dot product of two vectors A and B is equal to the product of magnitude of A and B and __________?","id":"9713ee39-9dcc-4e4d-9ce7-fd820911f0b3"},{"answers":["One thousandth","One millionth","One hundredth","One ten thousandth"],"correct_answer_id":1,"question":"What fraction of a millimeter is a nanometer?","id":"04d5dd73-1dba-41ad-be85-e1d2d22c58bd"},{"answers":["Euclid","Lao Tzu","Pythagorus","Kapil Dev"],"correct_answer_id":2,"question":"Who is considered the father of Mathematics?","id":"dee17ba5-4870-44e6-9b26-89f6c9cc28cf"},{"answers":["Srinivasa Ramanujan","Paul Erdos","John Napier","Georg Ferdinand Cantor"],"correct_answer_id":2,"question":"Which Scottish mathematician invented logarithms?","id":"b37c4f37-e158-474f-8586-30ef4e1e27d3"},{"answers":[" Hypotenuse","Hypothesis","Hypocrite","Hypnosis"],"correct_answer_id":0,"question":" What is the name for the longest side of a right-angled triangle?","id":"74ea4641-2aaa-41d7-a177-c21a669f771a"}],[{"answers":["Vitamin D","Vitamin E","Vitamin K","Vitamin B"],"correct_answer_id":1,"question":"Which Vitamin is also known as Tocopherol?","id":"53b18739-d3cc-4930-8b30-c3142c857518"},{"answers":["Carbohydrates","Proteins","Vitamins","All the above"],"correct_answer_id":1,"question":"Amino acids join together to make polypeptides. What polypeptides make by joining together?","id":"c6c24a17-ba01-4f54-8ac6-6abb709f0cb3"},{"answers":["Protein","Carbohydrate","Fats","Minerals"],"correct_answer_id":2,"question":"1 gm of which of the following will produce maximum ATPs?","id":"f21fb278-e3f2-4042-a27d-3732ee4ad85b"},{"answers":["85%","90%","94%","99%"],"correct_answer_id":3,"question":"What fraction of Body’s calcium is stored in Bones and teeth?","id":"f969a88c-28de-43b4-8254-8d9b070ba534"},{"answers":["Fruit","Cotyledons","Endosperm","Embryo"],"correct_answer_id":2,"question":"Which among the following is the edible part in Rice?","id":"2a8f7a3e-ba9e-4d4f-a32d-0ece311dcb05"}],[{"answers":["Silver","Copper","Lead","Mercury"],"correct_answer_id":2,"question":"Which of the following is the poorest conductor of heat in comparison to other options?","id":"41037029-47c1-408d-89b6-86b1f8b1c56a"},{"answers":["CaO","CaCO3","Ca(OH)2","CaCl2"],"correct_answer_id":0,"question":"Which among the following is known as Quick Lime?","id":"0f8b1df9-70d1-4d88-9774-07006c1a8a4a"},{"answers":["Acetic acid","Chloroform","Caustic Soda","Methane"],"correct_answer_id":2,"question":"Which of these is NOT a compound of carbon?","id":"8ecf8fab-52b2-4685-a231-b6a4f16cd405"},{"answers":["Evaporation","Sublimation","Simple Distillation","All of the above"],"correct_answer_id":1,"question":"Which method will is most suitable to separate the mixture of ammonium chloride and salt?","id":"1aa96d2f-b594-44e1-b992-13a938d4c030"},{"answers":["Simple Distillation","Fractional Distillation","Crystallisation","Chromatography"],"correct_answer_id":0,"question":"Which method is used to separate the components of a mixture containing two miscible liquids having sufficient difference in their boiling points?","id":"ad823e83-21e4-4b37-9224-13f3d4e4589b"}],[{"answers":["On Hard Disk","On Extension board","On Motherboard","On USB"],"correct_answer_id":2,"question":" Where is RAM placed?","id":"17e6b18a-ef37-4f13-93fd-61225f724782"},{"answers":["Ensures you never download any internet files."," Removes all viruses and trojans from your system.","Blocks your access to the internet.","Enhances your computer's protection against online threats."],"correct_answer_id":3,"question":"What is one of the primary functions of internet security software in relation to your computer's protection?","id":"995fc54a-5808-488c-8235-62a70f2288b6"},{"answers":["So that if you lose files you have a copy of them?"," So if you delete something if you still have it?"," So if you lose your computer you have a backup/copy?","If your computer goes wrong you have a backup?"],"correct_answer_id":3,"question":"Why are you recommended to back up your files?","id":"ef54ac96-b9b7-42e9-b9f0-de8c6a5fbd15"},{"answers":["Write your name","Put the date","Write the subject","Put a stamp on it"],"correct_answer_id":2,"question":"How should you start an email?","id":"b8ba9e8e-f6cb-49bc-bc76-f845d03c0323"},{"answers":["Safari","Chrome","Facebook","Firefox"],"correct_answer_id":2,"question":"Which one of the following is NOT a web browser?","id":"78f3b95b-81ff-42e1-96b7-c0ac9ccc5e6e"}]]